Architecture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Renaissance France (Box 22)
  - Cities (Box 22)
    - Paris (Box 23)
      - Hotels (Box 24)
        - Thelusson (Box 24)
        - Uzes (Box 24)
        - Vrilliere (Box 24)
      - Houses (Box 24)
      - Housing (Box 24)
      - Libraries (Box 24)
      - Markets (Box 24)
      - Museums (Box 24)
        - Louvre (Box 24)
          - General Exterior Views (Box 24)
          - Historic Views (Box 24)
          - Plans [Slide box 142] (Box 24)
          - Elevations (Box 24)
          - Exterior (Box 24)
            - East Side (Box 24)
            - Seine (South) Side (Box 24)
            - West Side (Box 24)
          - Interior (Box 24)
          - Court (Box 24)
            - East Side (Box 24)
            - West Side (Box 24)
          - Petite Galerie (Box 24)
      - Palaces [Slide boxes 142-143] (Box 24)
        - Les Tuilleries [Slide box 143] (Box 24)
      - Parks (Box 24)
      - Schools (Box 24)
        - Institut de France (Box 24)
      - Squares (Box 24)
        - Concorde (Box 24)
        - Vendome (Box 24)
        - Vosges-Royal (Box 24)
    - Raincy (Box 24)
    - Rambouillet [Slide box 144] (Box 24)
    - Richelieu (Box 24)
    - Rocroi (Box 24)
    - Rueil (Box 24)
    - Saint-Cloud (Box 24)
    - S. Germain-en-Lay (Box 24)
    - Salses (Box 24)
    - Sceaux (Box 24)
    - Tarascon (Box 24)
    - Thiais (Box 24)
    - Toulouse (Box 24)
    - Usse (Box 24)
    - Valbonne (Box 24)
    - Vaux-le-Vicomte (Box 24)
      - Plans (Box 24)
      - Exterior (Box 24)
        - Entrance Façade (Box 24)
        - Garden Façade (Box 24)
      - Interior [Slide boxes 144-145] (Box 24–25)
      - Gardens [Slide box 145] (Box 25)
    - Versailles (Box 25)
      - Palace (Box 25)
        - Air Views (Box 25)
        - Exterior (Box 25)
          - Paris Façade (Box 25)
          - Garden Faça (Box 25)
        - Gardens, Parks, Fountains (Box 25)
          - Orangerie [Slide box 146] (Box 25)
          - Parterre du Nord (Box 25)
          - Tapis vert (Box 25)
          - Fetes, fireworks (Box 25)
          - Fountains (Box 25)
        - Interior (Box 25)
          - Bedroom of Louis XIV (Box 25)
          - Galerie des Glaces (Hall of Mirrors) [Slide boxes 146-147] (Box 25)
          - Gallery of the Battles [Slide box 147] (Box 25)
          - Queen's Antechamber (Box 25)
          - Queen's Chamber (Box 25)
          - Oeil-de-Boeuf (Box 25)
          - Salon of Queen Guards (Box 25)
          - Salon de Venus (Box 25)
          - Salon of War (de la Guerre) (Box 25)
          - Staircase (Box 25)
          - Chapel (Box 25)
          - Grand Trianon (Box 25)
          - Petit Trianon (Box 25)
          - Hameau (Box 25)
    - Villandry (Box 25)
    - Villefranche-de-Conflent (Box 25)
    - Vitry-le-Francois [Slide box 148] (Box 25)
    - Wideville (Box 25)
- Renaissance Germany (Box 25)
  - Architects (Box 25)
    - Gilly, Friedrich (Box 25)
    - Weinbrenner, Fridrich (Box 25)
  - Cities (Box 25)
    - Annaberg (Box 25)
    - Attel (Box 25)
    - Augsburg (Box 25)
    - Ascaffenburg (Box 25)
    - Banz (Box 25)
    - Bayreuth [Slide box 149] (Box 25)
    - Benrath (Box 25)
    - Berg-am-Laim (Box 25)
    - Berlin (Box 25)
    - Birnau (Box 25)
    - Bonn (Box 25)
    - Braunschweig (Box 25)
    - Bruchsal (Box 25)
    - Bruhl (Box 25)
      - Schloss (Box 25)
        - Exterior (Box 25)
        - Interior (Box 25)
    - Buckeburg (Box 25)
    - Cassel (Box 25)
    - Celle (Box 25)
    - Diessen (Box 25)
    - Dresden [Slide boxes 149-150] (Box 25)
    - Dyhernfurth [Slide box 150] (Box 25)
    - Ettal (Box 25)
    - Freiburg (Box 25)
    - Fulda (Box 25)
    - Furstenfeldbruck (Box 25)
    - Gmund (Box 25)
    - Goessweinstein (Box 25)
    - Gorlitz (Box 25)
    - Guenzburg (Box 25)
    - Heidelberg (Box 25)
    - Hildescheim (Box 25)
    - Karlsruhe (Box 25)
    - Kempton (Box 25)
    - Landsberg (Box 25)
    - Landshut (Box 25)
    - Lemgo (Box 25)
    - Ludwigsburg (Box 25)
    - Mainz (Box 25)
    - Maria Birnbaum (Box 25)
    - Munich (Box 25)
      - Churches (Box 25)
        - Theatiner Church (Box 25)
        - S. John Nepomuk [Slide boxes 150-151] (Box 25–26)
      - Palaces [Slide box 151] (Box 26)
        - Residenz (Box 26)
      - Theater (Box 26)
    - Mussenhausen (Box 26)
    - Neresheim (Box 26)
    - Nuremburg (Box 26)
    - Nymphenberg Castle (Box 26)
      - Exterior (Box 26)
      - Interior (Box 26)
        - Amalienburg (Box 26)
        - Rondel (Box 26)
    - Obermarchtal (Box 26)
    - Ottobeuren (Box 26)
      - Abbey Church (Box 26)
        - Exterior [Slide box 152] (Box 26)
        - Interior (Box 26)
    - Pommersfelden (Box 26)
    - Potsdam (Box 26)
      - New Palace (Box 26)
      - Sans Souci (Box 26)
      - Park and Garden Buildings [Slide box 152-153] (Box 26)
    - Rohr [Slide box 153] (Box 26)
    - Rothenburg (Box 26)
    - Rot an der Ro (Box 26)
    - Rott-am-Inn (Box 26)
    - Sackingen (Box 26)
    - Schleissheim (Box 26)
    - Schontal im Jagsttal (Box 26)
    - Schwabisch Hall (Box 26)
    - Schussenried (Box 26)
    - Schwetzingen (Box 26)
    - Stadthagen (Box 26)
    - Steingaden (Box 26)
    - Steinhausen (Box 26)
    - Stuttgart (Box 26)
    - Tegernsee (Box 26)
    - Torgau (Box 26)
    - Trier (Box 26)
    - Ueberlingen (Box 26)
    - Veitschochheim (Box 26)
    - Vierzehnheiligen [Slide box 154] (Box 26)
    - Weimar (Box 26)
    - Weingarten (Box 26)
    - Weltenburg (Box 26)
    - Weyarn (Box 26)
    - Wiblingen (Box 26)
    - Wies (Box 26)
    - Worlitz (Box 26)
    - Wurzburg [Slide box 155] (Box 26)
      - Castle (Residenz) (Box 26)
        - Exterior (Box 26)
        - Interior (Box 26)
      - Neumunster Church (Box 26)
      - Schonborn (Box 26)
    - Zwiefalten (Box 26)
      - Church (Box 26)
        - Exterior (Box 26)
        - Interior (Box 26)
- Renaissance Greece (Box 26)
  - Nauplion (Box 26)
  - Navarino (Box 26)
- Renaissance Italy (Box 26)
  [Slide box 156]
  - General (Box 26)
  - Architects (Box 26)
    - Alberti, L.B. (Box 26)
    - Antolini, G. (Box 26)
    - Bernini (Box 26)
    - Bibiena family (Box 26)
    - Bramante (Box 26)
    - Brunelleschi (Box 26)
    - Cesariano (Box 26)
    - Filarete (Box 26)
    - Fontana, Carlo [Slide box 157] (Box 27)
    - Francesco di Giorgio (Box 27)
    - Gioffredo, Mario (Box 27)
    - Guarini, Guarino (Box 27)
    - Juvara, Filippo (Box 27)
    - Leonardo da Vinci (Box 27)
    - Michelangelo [Slide box 158] (Box 27)
    - Palladio, Andrea (Box 27)
    - Peruzzi, Balda (Box 27)
    - Rossellino, Bernardo (Box 27)
    - San Gallo, Guiliano (Box 27)
    - San Gallo, Guiliano (Box 27)
    - Serlio, Sebastiano [Slide boxes 158-159] (Box 27)
    - Vanvitelli, L. [Slide box 159] (Box 27)
  - Cities (Box 27)
    - Aquila (Box 27)
    - Arezzo (Box 27)
      - S. Annunziata (Box 27)
    - Ariccia (Box 27)
    - Artimino (Box 27)
    - Bagnaia (Box 27)
      - Villa Lante (Box 27)
    - Bagnolo (Box 27)
    - Bassano (Box 27)
    - Bergamo (Box 27)
    - Bertesina (Box 27)
    - Bologna (Box 27)
      - Churches (Box 27)
      - Palaces [Slide boxes 159-160] (Box 27)
    - Bomarzo [Slide box 160] (Box 27)
    - Bra (Box 27)
    - Brendola (Box 27)
    - Brescia (Box 27)
    - Cadenabbia (Box 27)
    - Caldogno (Box 27)
    - Camaldoli (Box 27)
    - Campiglia (Box 27)
    - Caprarola (Box 27)
      - Palazzo Farnese (Box 27)
        - Exterior (Box 27)
        - Courtyard (Box 27)
        - Interior (Box 27)
        - Gardens: Palazzina (Box 27)
    - Careggi (Box 27)
    - Carignano (Box 27)
    - Carpi (Box 27)
    - Caserta (Box 27)
      - Palazzo Reale (Box 27)
        - Plans, Sections, Drawings, Design (Box 27)
        - Exterior (Box 27)
        - Garden (Box 27)
        - Interior [Slide box 162] (Box 27)
    - Castiglione Olona (Box 27)
    - Castello (Box 27)
    - Castle Gandolfo (Box 27)
    - Cernobbio (Box 27)
    - Certaldo (Box 27)
    - Citta di Castello (Box 27)
    - Collodi (Box 27)
    - Crema (Box 27)
    - Cricoli (Box 27)
    - Faenza (Box 27)
    - Fano (Box 27)
    - Fanzolo (Box 27)
    - Ferrara (Box 27)
    - Plans [Slide boxes 162-163] (Box 27–28)
      - Churches [Slide box 163] (Box 28)
      - Palaces (Box 28)
    - Fiesole (Box 28)
    - Finale di Agugliaro (Box 28)
    - Florence (Box 28)
      - General (Box 28)
        - Maps and Plans (Box 28)
        - Views (Box 28)
      - Bridges [Slide box 164] (Box 28)
      - Churches (Box 28)
      - Cathedral (Box 28)
        - Dome (Box 28)
        - Lantern (Box 28)
        - Church of the Ognissanti (Box 28)
        - SS. Annunziata (Box 28)
        - S. Croce (Box 28)
        - Pazzi Chapel (Box 28)
          - Plans (Box 28)
          - Exterior [Slide boxes 164-165] (Box 28)
          - Interior [Slide box 165] (Box 28)
        - S. Felicita (Box 28)
        - S. Lorenzo (Box 28)
          - Plans and Sections (Box 28)
          - Façade Designs (Box 28)
          - Exterior (Box 28)
          - Interior (Box 28)
            - Chapel of the Princes (Box 28)
            - New Sacristy (Medici Chapel) (Box 28)
            - Old Sacristy [Slide box 166] (Box 28)
        - S. Marco (Box 28)
        - S. Maria degli Angeli (Box 28)
        - S. Maria del Carmine (Box 28)
        - S. Maria Maddalena (Box 28)
        - S. Maria Novella (Box 28)
        - S. Miniato al Monte: Chapel of the Cardinal of Portugal (Box 28)
        - S. Pancrazio (Box 28)
        - S. Spirito (Box 28)
          - Plans, Sections, and Models (Box 28)
            - Interior [Slide box 167] (Box 28)
      - Hospitals (Box 28)
        - Hospital of the Innocent (Box 28)
      - Houses (Box 28)
      - Loggia (Box 28)
      - Palaces (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Alberti (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Antinori (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Bardi di Vernio (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Bartolini (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Capponi delle Rovinate (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Cocchi (Box 28)
        - Palazzo dell'Antella (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Dello Strozino (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Fenzi [Slide box 168] (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Fiaschi-Cuccoli (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Gondi (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Giugni (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Guadagni (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Horne (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Larderel (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Medici-Riccardi (Box 28)
          - Exterior (Box 28)
          - Interior (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Nonfinito (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Pandolfini (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Pazzi-Quaratesi (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Pitti (Box 28)
          - Exterior (Box 28)
          - Interior (Box 28)
          - Gardens (Box 28)
        - Palazzo Portinari-Salviati [Slide box 169] (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Rucellai (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Scala-della-Gherardesca (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Strozzi (Box 29)
          - Plans and Sections (Box 29)
          - Exterior (Box 29)
          - Interior (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Uffizi (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Vecchio (Box 29)
          - Interior (Box 29)
            - Studiolo of Francis I (Box 29)
      - Squares (Box 29)
        - Piazza Della Signoria (Box 29)
        - Villas [Slide box 170] (Box 29)
    - Fondi (Box 29)
    - Frascati (Box 29)
      - Villas (Box 29)
      - Villa Aldobrandini (Box 29)
      - Villa Mondragone (Box 29)
      - Villa Torlonia (Box 29)
    - Fratta Polesine (Box 29)
    - Fumane (Box 29)
    - Galluzzo (Box 29)
    - Genoa (Box 29)
      - Churches (Box 29)
      - Palaces (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Balbi (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Doria-Pamphili (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Doria-Tursi (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Durazzo (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Ducale (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Grimaldi (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Lercari-Parodi (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Pallavicini (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Podesta [Slide box 171] (Box 29)
        - Palazzo San Giorgio (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Spinola (Box 29)
      - Villas (Box 29)
    - Gubbio (Box 29)
    - Lago Maggiore (Box 29)
    - Lecce (Box 29)
    - Livorno (Box 29)
    - Lonedo (Box 29)
    - Lonigo (Box 29)
    - Loreto (Box 29)
    - Lucca (Box 29)
    - Lugo (Box 29)
    - Luvigliano (Box 29)
    - Macerata (Box 29)
    - Mantua (Box 29)
      - Casa di Giulio Romano (Box 29)
      - Churches (Box 29)
        - S. Andrea [Slide box 172] (Box 29)
      - Palaces (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Communale (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Ducale (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Del Te (Box 29)
          - Exterior (Box 29)
          - Interior (Box 29)
          - Grotto (Box 29)
        - Palazzo Vecchio (Box 29)
          - Squares (Box 29)
    - Maser [Slide boxes 172-173] (Box 29)
    - Matera [Slide box 173] (Box 29)
    - Meledo (Box 29)
    - Milan (Box 29)
      - Churches (Box 29)
        - S. Maria delle Grazie (Box 29)
        - S. Maria Presso, S. Celso (Box 29)
        - S. Maria Presso, S. Satiro (Box 29)
      - Palaces (Box 29)
      - Villas (Box 29)
        - Villa Reale-Belgioioso (Box 29)
    - Mira (Box 29)
      - Villa Foscari [Slide boxes 173-174] (Box 29)
    - Mongiovino [Slide box 174] (Box 29)
    - Montagnana (Box 29)
    - Montecchio (Box 29)
    - Montepulciano (Box 29)
      - Churches (Box 29)
        - S. Biagio (Box 29)
      - Palaces (Box 29)
    - Naples (Box 29)
      - Churches (Box 29)
        - Cappella Sansevero [Slide box 175] (Box 30)
      - Cathedral (Box 30)
      - S. Giovanni a Carbonara (Box 30)
      - Certosa di S. Martino (Monastery) (Box 30)
      - Chiesa di Monteoliveto (Box 30)
      - Gates (Box 30)
      - Palaces (Box 30)
        - Castel Nuovo (Box 30)
        - Palazzo di Capodi (Box 30)
        - Palazzo Reale (Box 30)
      - Villas (Box 30)
        - Poggioreale (Box 30)
    - Noto (Sicily) (Box 30)
    - Orgiano [Slide box 176] (Box 30)
    - Orvieto (Box 30)
    - Ostia (Box 30)
    - Padua (Box 30)
    - Palermo (Box 30)
    - Palmanova (Box 30)
    - Parma (Box 30)
    - Pavia (Box 30)
      - Cathedral (Box 30)
      - Certosa (Box 30)
      - Perugia (Box 30)
      - Pesaro (Box 30)
      - Petraia (Box 30)
      - Piazza Armerina (Box 30)
      - Piena (Box 30)
        - Churches (Box 30)
        - Palaces (Box 30)
          - Palazzo Piccolomini [Slide boxes 176-177] (Box 30)
          - Palazzo Vescovile [Slide box 177] (Box 30)
      - Piombino Dese (Box 30)
      - Pisa (Box 30)
      - Pistoia (Box 30)
      - Poggia a Caiano (Box 30)
      - Poiana Maggiore (Box 30)
      - Pordenone (Box 30)
      - Posillipo (Box 30)
      - Pozzuoli (Box 30)
      - Prato (Box 30)
      - Quinto (Box 30)
      - Rimini (Box 30)
        - Exterior (Box 30)
        - Interior (Box 30)
      - Rome (Box 30)
        - General [Slide boxes 177-178] (Box 30)
        - Plans [Slide box 178] (Box 30)
          - Sixtus V Plan (Box 30)
          - 1551 Plan by Bufalini (Box 30)
          - Plan of 1557 (Box 30)
          - 1593 Plans by Tempesta (Box 30)
          - 1661-2 Plan by Tempesta (Box 30)
        - Views (Box 30)
        - Streets (Box 30)
        - Castel S. Angelo [Slide box 179] (Box 30)
        - Churches (Box 30)
          - Seven (Pilgrimage) Churches (Box 30)
          - Collegio di Propaganda Fide (Box 30)
            - Exterior (Box 30)
            - Interior (Box 30)
          - Collegio Romani (Box 30)
          - Il Gesu (Box 30)
            - Exterior (Box 30)
            - Interior (Box 30)
          - Oratorio di S. Filippo Neri (Box 30)
          - S. Agnese [Slide box 180] (Box 30)
            - Exterior (Box 30)
            - Interior (Box 30)
          - S. Agostino (Box 30)
          - S. Andrea al Quirinale (Box 30)
          - S. Andrea delle Fratte (Box 30)
          - S. Andrea Della Valle (Box 30)
          - S. Andrea in Via Flaminia (Box 30)
          - S. Carlo al Corso (Box 30)
          - S. Carloalle Quattre Fontane (Box 30)
            - Cloister (Box 30)
            - Interior [Slide box 181] (Box 31)
          - S. Caterina dei Funari (Box 31)
          - S. Caterina a Magnanapoli (Box 31)
          - S. Cecilia (Box 31)
          - S. Croce in Gerusalemme (Box 31)
          - S. Elegio degli Orefici (Box 31)
          - S. Francesco a Ripa (Box 31)
          - S. Giacomo in Augusta (Box 31)
          - S. Giacomo degli Incurabili (Box 31)
          - S. Giacomo degli Spagnuoli (Box 31)
          - S. Giovanni dei Fiorentini (Box 31)
          - S. Giovanni in Laterano (Box 31)
          - S. Giovanni in Olio (Box 31)
          - S. Girolamo Della Carita (Box 31)
          - S. Girolamo degli Schiavoni (Box 31)
          - S. Gregorio (Box 31)
          - S. Ignazio [Slide box 182] (Box 31)
          - S. Ivo Della Sapienza (Box 31)
            - Exterior (Box 31)
            - Interior (Box 31)
          - S. Luca e Martina (Box 31)
          - S. Marcello (Box 31)
          - S. Marcello (Box 31)
          - S. Maria Aventina (Box 31)
          - S. Maria in Compitelli (Box 31)
          - S. Maria Della Consolazione [Slide box 183] (Box 31)
          - S. Maria di Loreto (Box 31)
          - S. Maria Maddalena (Box 31)
          - S. Maria Maggiore (Box 31)
          - S. Maria dei Miracoli (Box 31)
          - S. Maria di Monte Santo (Box 31)
          - S. Maria dell'Orazione (Box 31)
          - S. Maria dell'Orto (Box 31)
          - S. Maria Della Pace (Box 31)
          - S. Maria Del Popolo (Box 31)
          - S. Maria Del Priorato (Box 31)
          - S. Maria de' Sette Dolori (Box 31)
          - S. Maria Sopra Minerva (Box 31)
          - S. Maria in Traspontina (Box 31)
          - S. Maria in Vallicella (Box 31)
          - S. Maria in Via Lata (Box 31)
          - S. Maria Della Vittoria (Box 31)
          - S. Nicola in Carcere [Slide box 184] (Box 31)
          - S. Nome di Maria (Box 31)
          - S. Onofrio (Box 31)
          - S. Pasquale (Box 31)
          - S. Peter's (Box 31)
            - General (Box 31)
              - Drawings (Box 31)
                - Sections (Box 31)
                - Elevations (Box 31)
                - Medals (Box 31)
                - Models [Slide box 184-185] (Box 31)
                - Plans [Slide box 185] (Box 31)
                - Vatican Library Frescoes (Box 31)
              - Air Views (Box 31)
              - Piazza [Slide boxes 185-186] (Box 31)
                - Colonnade [Slide box 186] (Box 31)
                - Obelisk (Box 31)
                - View from Dome (Box 31)
              - Exterior (Box 31)
                - Façade (Box 31)
                - Details (Box 31)
                - Dome (Box 31)
              - Interior [Slide box 187] (Box 32)
                - Details (Box 32)
                - Baldacchino (Box 32)
                - Dome (Box 32)
          - S. Pietro in Montorio (Box 32)
            - Tempietto (Box 32)
          - S. Rita (Box 32)
          - S. Sebastiano (Box 32)
          - Santo Spirito in Sassis [Slide box 188] (Box 32)
          - S. Susanna (Box 32)
          - S. Trinita Del Monte (Box 32)
          - S. Trinita Del Monte (Box 32)
          - S. Trinita dei Pelligrini (Box 32)
          - S. Vicenzo e Anatasio (Box 32)
            - Fountains (Box 32)
              - Fontana di Trevi (Box 32)
              - Fountain of the Tortoises (Box 32)
        - Gates (Box 32)
          - Porta Pia (Box 32)
        - Hospitals (Box 32)
        - Palaces (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Barberini [Slide boxes 188-189] (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Del Bufalo [Slide box 189] (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Cancelleria (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Farnese (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Giraud (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Lateran (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Massimo alle Colonne (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Del Quirinale (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Riaro (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Spada (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Venezi [Slide box 190] (Box 32)
          - Zucceri Palace (Box 32)
        - Prisons (Box 32)
        - Squares and Piazzas (Box 32)
          - Piazza Del Campidoglio (Box 32)
          - General Views (Box 32)
          - Capitoline Museum (Box 32)
          - Palazzo dei Conservatori (Box 32)
          - Palazzo Senatorio (Box 32)
          - Piazza Navona [Slide boxes 190-191] (Box 32)
          - Piazza Del Popolo [Slide box 191] (Box 32)
          - Piazza Del Quirinale (Box 32)
          - Piazza S. Ignazio (Box 32)
          - Piazza di Spagna (Box 32)
        - Vatican (Box 32)
          - Plans (Box 32)
          - Exterior (Box 32)
          - Interior (Box 32)
            - Belvedere [Slide boxes 191-192] (Box 32)
            - Casino of Pius IV (Villa Pia) [Slide box 192] (Box 32)
            - Loggetta (Box 32)
            - Scala Regua (Box 32)
            - Sistine Chapel (Box 32)
        - Villas (Box 32)
          - Villa Albani (Box 32)
          - Villa Belvedere (Box 32)
          - Villa Borghese (Box 32)
          - Villa Doria-Pamphili [Slide box 193] (Box 33)
          - Villa Farnesina (Box 33)
          - Villa Giulia (Box 33)
            - Entrance Façade (Box 33)
            - First Court (Box 33)
            - Second Court (Box 33)
          - Villa Madama (Box 33)
            - Interior (Box 33)
          - Villa Medici [Slide boxes 193-194] (Box 33)
    - Roncade [Slide box 194] (Box 33)
    - Sabbioneta (Box 33)
    - Sampierdarena (Box 33)
    - Sansepolcro (Box 33)
    - S. Gregorio da Sassola (Box 33)
    - S. Leo (Box 33)
    - Santa Sophia (Box 33)
    - Siena (Box 33)
    - Stra (Box 33)
    - Stupinigi (Box 33)
    - Subianco (Box 33)
    - Syracuse (Box 33)
    - Tivoli (Box 33)
      - Villa d'Este (Box 33)
        - Interiors (Box 33)
        - Gardens [Slide boxes 194-195] (Box 33)
          - Dragon Fountain [Slide box 195] (Box 33)
          - Fountain Walk (Box 33)
          - Rometta Fountain (Box 33)
          - Tivoli (Oval) Fountain (Box 33)
          - Water Organ Fountain (Box 33)
    - Todi (Box 33)
      - S. Maria della Consolazione (Box 33)
    - Trent (Box 33)
    - Turin (Box 33)
      - Churches (Box 33)
        - Cathedral of Giovanni Battista [Slide box 196] (Box 33)
        - S. Lorenzo (Box 33)
        - S. Maria di Piazza (Box 33)
        - Superga (Box 33)
      - Palaces (Box 33)
        - Palazzo Carignano (Box 33)
        - Palazzo Madama (Box 33)
    - Udine (Box 33)
    - Urbino (Box 33)
      - Palaces (Box 33)
        - Palazzo Ducale (Box 33)
          - Exterior (Box 33)
          - Interior (Box 33)
    - Vallinotto (Box 33)
    - Vancimuglio (Box 33)
    - Venice (Box 33)
      - Plans (Box 33)
      - Views (Box 33)
        - Air Views (Box 33)
      - Bridges (Box 33)
      - Churches (Box 33)
        - S. Francesco Della Vigna (Box 33)
        - S. Giobbe (Box 33)
        - S. Giorgio Maggiore (Box 33)
          - Exterior (Box 33)
          - Interior [Slide boxes 197-198] (Box 33)
          - Exterior Sculpture [Slide box 198] (Box 33)
        - S. Giovanni Crisostomo (Box 33)
        - S. Maria Della Carita (Box 33)
        - S. Maria dei Miracoli (Box 33)
        - S. Maria Della Salute (Box 33)
        - S. Maria Formosa (Box 33)
        - S. Maria Maddalena (Box 33)
        - S. Michele in Isola (Box 33)
        - IL Redentore (Box 33)
          - Exterior (Box 33)
          - Interior (Box 33)
        - S. Simone Piccolo [Slide box 199] (Box 34)
      - Government Buildings (Box 34)
        - Arsenal (Box 34)
      - Libraries (Box 34)
        - Libreria di S. Marco (Box 34)
          - Exterior (Box 34)
          - Interior (Box 34)
      - Palaces (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Bernardo (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Grimani (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Corner della Ca'Grande (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Ducale [Slide box 200] (Box 34)
          - Courtyard and Giant's Staircase (Box 34)
          - Interior (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Vendramin-Calergi (Box 34)
      - Schools (Box 34)
        - Scuola S. Giovanni (Box 34)
        - Scuola S. Marco (Box 34)
        - Scuola S. Rocco (Box 34)